JACOB DAVIS

FULL STACK DEVELOPER



https://wickerprison.github.io/FullstackPortfolio/

CONTACT



(435) 294-8060



Cobylax17@gmail.com



122 E Sego Lily Dr. Apt 316, Sandy, UT, 84070

SUMMARY

I am a full stack developer with strong math and problem solving skills. I love understanding and building complex systems. I have been programming in various contexts for several years and am constantly learning new skills and applying existing skills in new ways.

SKILLS

- React, JavaScript, JQuery
- Node.js, express
- C#, .NET
- HTML, Bootstrap, Handlebars
- CSS
- SQL (MySQL, PostgreSQL)
- NoSQL (MongoDB)
- · Object Oriented Programming
- MVC Design Pattern
- GitHub
- Advanced Math

WORK EXPERIENCE

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Brigham Young University

2016 - 2022

- Wrote MATLAB code for modeling and analyzing complex ion trajectories
- Published a first author paper in the journal Organometallics
- Excelled in graduate level quantum mechanics classes

TEACHING ASSISTANT

Brigham Young University

2019 - 2022

- Taught introductory MATLAB coding course for six semesters
- Wrote new programming teaching material and assignments

EDUCATION

FULL STACK DEVELOPMENT BOOT CAMP

University of Utah 2023 - 2024

MASTERS - PHYSICAL CHEMISTRY

Brigham Young University Gpa - 3.9

2020 - 2022

BACHELORS - CHEMISTRY

Brigham Young University GPA - 3.9

2016 - 2020

OTHER EXPERIENCE

CO-FOUNDER/LEAD DEVELOPER BROKEN BEAKER STUDIO

2021 - Present

- Created an indie video game with a small team
- Created many systems, enemy Als, and player abilities in C#
- First game will soon be available for purchase on Steam: https://store.steampowered.com/app/2381770/Arcane Audit/

PERSONAL PROJECTS

- Created many web apps and other programming projects
- My portfolio: https://wickerprison.github.io/FullstackPortfolio/